Daniel Burgess

Full Stack Developer

0434 869 784

github.com/DBurgess93

danielburgessportfolio.herokuapp.com

dan-burgess@hotmail.com

linkedin.com/in/daniel-burgess-668176186/

Professional Summary

Ambitious, reliable and functionality first Full-Stack Developer. Looking to engage in a new team environment and apply programming skills, as well as build upon knowledge base in the interest of ongoing improvement. Recent graduate of Le Wagon Coding Bootcamp, skilled in both front-end and back-end programming languages/frameworks, as well as databases to build fully functional web applications with a focus on user experience and optimal performance. Portfolio includes both team and individual projects taken from initial design to deployment, using tools to track progress and organise team workflow.

Previous work includes 8 years in sales and customer relations roles, 6 years in heavily team-based roles, experience in teaching workplace processes, leading small teams and working autonomously.

Previous employees would endorse for having a great attitude, being a hard worker, a people person and someone who is curious and eager to learn.

Summary of Skills

Technical Skills

- Tech-stack includes Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, React (ongoing), Stimulus Framework, PostgreSQL, HTML, SCSS, Bootstrap and Figma.
- Experience using API's and web scraping.
- GitHub
- Trello
- Figma
- User experience with Sales, CRM, Logistics, and machine Operating programs in previous roles.

Soft Skills

- Great communication
- Organisation
- Collaborative
- Leadership
- Adaptability
- Problem solving
- Curiosity
- Highly Personable

Education

WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE 2022Le Wagon

DIPLOMA OF REMEDIAL MASSAGE 2015Endeavour College of Natural Health

HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATE - 2011

Nuriootpa High School

References can be provided upon request

Projects

Deepwork

- A Web-app designed to help students track how they spend their study time, analyse their data for a better understanding of their studying habits and motivate them to reach a state of deep focus.
- Tech-stack: Ruby on Rails, SASS, HTML, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Figma.

<u>De-fit</u>

- A Webapp built to help bring together those who are in need of a fitness space and those who have one to share.
- Tech-stack: Ruby on Rails, SASS, HTML, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Figma.

The Odin Project

 Currently working through The Odin Project online, with the aim of improving JavaScript skillset, learning React, and building an array of different projects along the way to improve the portfolio.

Work Experience

Internal Sales | Amorini Australia | Aug 2021 - Sep 2022

- Managing all custom-made kitchen parts for every order.
- First point of call for customers, communicating to ensure custom products meet specification requirements.
- Tracking and ordering for stock holdings.
- Logistics Coordinating stock compiling for orders to be sent to site and between factories.
- Data entry using Servicem8 and EQ Business Management Software.

Sales Rep | Camfil Australia (Airepure) | Jun 2018 - Dec 2019

- Building and maintaining customer relations through Sales calls and communication.
- Collaborated with internal engineering teams to provide product and technical advice to customers.
- Reading through tender documents and quoting for projects from mechanical contractors.
- Sales research to secure early sales/tenders.
- Stock control, re-ordering, cycle-counts, and regular stock takes.
- Logistics co-ordination.
- Data entry using Sage Accpac and Realtime Logistics.

Remedial Therapist | Own Business | Mar 2014 - Jun 2018

- Providing Remedial services to clients.
- Business management.
- Point of sale and invoicing using Square.
- Growing and maintaining client base through advertising, networking and social media engagement.
- Appointment tracking using various software products including Power Diary and Cliniko Practice Management.

Other Roles

Mapping operator | Voxel Maps | Jan 2023 - Mar 2023 Cellar hand | Treasure Wine Estates | Jan 2020 - Aug 2021 Delivery Driver | OzHarvest | April 2020 - Oct 2020 Duty Manager | Barossa Rex Centre | Jan 2012 - Aug 2015